You can't show up to a dirt bike event you never discover, and honestly, that's what I felt as a new rider.
你无法参加一场你从未发现的越野摩托活动，说实话，这就是我当年作为新手车友的感受。
If you don't already know the track name, follow the right Instagram page, or know somebody who's plugged in,
如果你本来就不知道赛道名字，没有关注对的 Instagram 主页，也不认识圈内的熟人，
you might just never find out there's a ride day happening right next to you.
你可能永远不会发现，就在你旁边正在举行一场骑行日活动。
And that's one of the reasons why I'm building DirtBikeX.
这也正是我打造 DirtBikeX 的原因之一。
I want tracks to be easier to find, and exactly where riders are looking.
我希望赛道更容易被找到，而且就出现在车友们正在寻找的地方。
Here, if you run a dirt bike track, you can get verified as a track owner so riders know your updates are real.
在这里，如果你经营一条越野摩托赛道，你可以认证成为赛道主，让车友知道你发布的更新是真实的。
You can create ride days, races, open practices, and even reoccurring events.
你可以创建骑行日、比赛、自由练习，甚至是重复举办的活动。
Then, fellow riders can find them in the Events tab, filter what's nearby, RSVP, and get reminded before it starts.
然后，其他车友可以在「活动」标签页里找到它们，筛选附近的活动，报名参加，并在开始前收到提醒。
The idea is simple, help riders find places to ride, and help tracks to get more people to show up.
想法很简单，帮助车友找到骑行的地方，也帮助赛道吸引更多人到场。
My name is Rubio, and if you're a track owner, comment "OWNER" and I'll send you the link!
我叫鲁比奥，如果你是赛道主，评论「OWNER」，我就把链接发给你！